God is still saying something.
On Sunday 31st of August 2014, Prophet T.B. Joshua gave a prophecy
concerning a military intervention in a Southern African country.
Let us listen to his words.
A president will be kidnapped; I mentioned it.
I mean, Southern African people will remember,
if they are not going to misquote me this time.
But this time, what I'm saying now -
quote me well; don't misquote me.
I am seeing military - they are still on that plan
to kidnap either the President, or Vice President of that nation,
or the First Lady of that nation.
They are aiming to do that and they are still serious to do it.
The plan is going on now.
If prayer is not offered well, they will succeed.
If he refuses the order, they will kill him.
That is what I'm seeing.
They should pray for Southern Africa - a president.
God showed me the place but I don't want to put any country into pandemonium.
But Southern Africa - they should pray for them.
Pray for them; God loves them.